HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/005 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Unidentified (slides) (Box 18, Folder 55)
  21 slides
- Unidentified slides (Box 18, Folder 56)
  14 slides
- Unidentified slides (Box 18, Folder 57)
  27 slides
- Unidentified slides (Box 18, Folder 58)
  13 slides
- Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Unidentified negatives (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Unidentified negatives (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Unidentified negatives (Box 18, Folder 62)
- unidentified negatives (Box 18, Folder 63)
- Unidentified negatives (Box 18, Folder 64)
- Unidentified slides (Box 18, Folder 65)
  33 slides
- Unidentified slides (Box 18, Folder 66)
  31 slides
- Local 1 - Chicago, Ill. (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Local 2 - San Francisco, CA (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Local 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Local 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Former Locals 9, 41, 38 and 48, 30, 110, 283 -- Now Local 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Local 4 - Buffalo, NY (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Former Locals 488 and 269 - Now Local 4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Local 5, Honolulu, HI (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Local 6 - New York, NY (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Former Local 1 - now Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Local 6 - Hotel Strike (Box 19, Folder 13)
- New York Trades Council - Now Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Local 6 - Race Relations Award to Little Rock (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Local 36 - Now Local 7 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Local 8 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  14 photographs - 1 CD pulled and placed in CD/DVD cabinet in Rm 415
- Former Locals 61 and 507 - Now Local 8 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Former Locals 3, 33, 487, 596 -- Now Local 8 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Local 9 - Portland, OR (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Former Locals 207, 452, 496, 664 - Now Local 9 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Local 10 - Macedonia, OH (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Former Locals 106, 108, 274 -- Now Local 10 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Former Local 8 and 17 - Now Local 11 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  8 slides; 48 photographs
- Former Local 440, 468 - Now Local 11 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Former Local 512, 639, 694, 765 - Now Local 11 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Local 12 (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Former Locals 68, 72, 177, 276, 363 - Now Local 12 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Local 14 - Denver, CO (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Local 15 (Southern, Illinois) (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Local 573 - Local 16 (Central, Illinois) (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Local 17 (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Former Locals 152, 286, 458, 556, 665 - now Local 17 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Local 18 - (Santa Rosa, CA) (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Local 19 (San Jose, CA) (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Local 180, 577 -- Now 19 (San Jose) (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Local 20 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Local 21 - Rochester, Minn. (Box 19, Folder 38)
  52 photographs
- Local 23 (Norfolk, VA) (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Local 24 - Detroit, Mich. (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Former Local 234 - Now Local 24 (Detroit, Mich.) (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Former Local 562 - Now Local 24 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Former Local 705 - Now Local 24 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Local 25 - Washington, D.C. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  38 photographs; newspaper articles
- Local 25 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Local 25 - Old Locals - 75, 80, 209, 423, 781 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Local 25 - Ban the lie detector (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Local 25 - Sept. 14 Contract Rally (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Local 25 - Jesse Jackson (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Madison Hotel Picket - Local 25 12/2/1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Local 25 - Retirees (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Local 25 - TV show (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Local 25 - Willard Hotel Strike (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Local 25 - Williamsburg 1989 - HERE Conference (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Local 26 - Boston, MA (Box 20, Folder 12)
  48 photographs; 5 slides
- Local 26 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  1 photograph - 1 CD removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet (now box 34)
- Local 26 - Boston, MA (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Local 27 - Binghamton, NY (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Park, Local 27 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Local 28 - Oakland, CA (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Local 28 - Oakland, CA (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Local 29 - (85, 90, 319) - Lawrence, MA (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Local 31's last meeting - Now Local 28 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Local 30 - San Diego (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Local 31 - Montreal, Quebec, Canada (Box 20, Folder 22)
  38 photographs; 1 slide
- Local 32 - Washington, DC (Box 20, Folder 23)
  97 photographs
- SEIU - Local 82 - HERE Local 32, January 19 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Local 33 (Local 170 changed to 33) (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Local 34 - New Haven, CT (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Local 35 - New Haven, CT (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Local 34 and 35 - YALE (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Local 37 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Local 40 - Vancouver, BC (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Former Local 28, 676 - Now Local 40 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Local 42 - S. Brooklyn, NY (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Local 47 - Edmonton, Canada - Calgary, Alta; 93?, 172 none, 265, 579 none (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Local 49 - Sacramento, CA (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Local 50 - Hayward, CA (Box 20, Folder 35)
  14 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Local 54 - Atlantic City, NJ (Box 20, Folder 36)
  35 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Local 54 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Local 54 - Diskettes w/pictures (Box 20, Folder 38)
  10 floppy discs
- Local 56 - Billings, MT (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Local 57 - Pittsburgh, PA (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Local 64 - Kansas City, MO (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Local 65 - Tucson, AZ (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Local 66 - Buffalo, NY (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Local 69 - Bergen County, NJ (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Local 11, 45, 60, 71, 159 -- Now Local 69 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  61 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Local 70 - Columbus/Dayton, OH - Indianapolis, IN (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Local 73 - Thunder Bay, Ontario, Canada (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Local 74 - St. Louis, MO (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Local 75 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Local 76 Monticello, NY (Box 21, Folder 11)
- local 82 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Local 84 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Local 86 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Local 88 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Local 88 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Local 89 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Local 99 - Duluth, MN. (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Local 99 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Local 100 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Local 101 - Great Falls, MT (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Local 122 - Milwaukee, WI (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Local 134 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Local 144 - Dec. 1985 - SZABO Contract (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Local 146 - Waterloo, IA (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Local 150 - Syracuse, NY (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Local 151 - Atlanta, GA (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Local 155 - Reading, PA (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Local 165 - Las Vegas (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Local 165 - Las Vegas (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Local 166 - New Orleans (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Local 181 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Local 206 - Winnipeg Man. Canada (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Local 217 - New Haven, CT. (Providence) (Box 21, Folder 34)
  46 photographs; 1 slide
- Local 220 - Eureka, Canada (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Local 226 - Las Vegas, NV (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Local 246 - Oklahoma City, OK (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Local 261 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Local 264 - Omaha, NE (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Local 267 - Wilmington, Del. (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Local 270 - Wilmington, Del (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Local 274 - Philadelphia, PA (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Local 280 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Local 301 - Philadelphia, PA (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Local 302 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Local 355 - (133, 255, 339) (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Local 355 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Local 360 - Longview, WA (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Local 369 - Albert Lea, MA (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Local 400 - Spokane, WA (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Local 425 - Vancouver, WA (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Local 427 - Missoula, MT (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Local 436 - Albuquerque (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Local 442 - Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Local 450 - Forest Park, Il (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Local 457 - Butte, MT (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Local 466, Rochester, NY (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Local 471 - Albany, NY (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Local 483 - Pacific Grove, CA (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Local 483 - Monterey, CA (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Local 497 - Cedar Rapids, IA (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Local 498 - Santa Barbara, CA (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Local 509 - Anaconda, MT (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Local 531 - Pasadena, CA (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Local 535 - Riverside, CA (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Local 550 - Bakersfield, CA (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Local 604 - Peterborough, Ontario, Canada (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Local 610 - San Juan, PR (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Local 610 - San Juan, PR (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Local 628 - El Paso, TX (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Local 631 - Phoenix, AZ (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Local 662 - Halifax, NS, Canada (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Local 681 - Long Beach, CA (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Local 681 - Disneyland, Fall 1955 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Local 703 - Santa Maria, CA (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Local 737 - Orlando, FL (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Local 767 - Saskatoon, Sask, Canada (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Local 779 (Sept. 1969) - St. John's, Newfoundland (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Local 814 - Santa Monica, CA (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Local 835 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Local 838 - Coos Bay, OR (Casper, WY?) (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Local 863 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Local 867 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Local 871 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Local 878 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Local 879 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Local 2850 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Local 309 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Local 310 - Rock Island, IL (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Local 312 - Kalispell, MT (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Local 315 - Wisconsin Rapids (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Local 325 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Local 335 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Local 340 - San Matco, CA (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Local 341 - Haure, MT (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Local 353 - Dallas, TX (Box 22, Folder 51)
  18 photographs; 2 slides
- Local 22 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Local 39 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Local 42 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Local 55 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Local 58 (also 303-merged) (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Local 60 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Local 61 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Local 66 (347 merged with 66, also 196 and 135) (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Local 96 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Local 103 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Local 104 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Local 107 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Local 109 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Local 112 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Local 116 (82, 773) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  2 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Local 117 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Local 129 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Local 163 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Local 170 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Local 187 - Madison, Wis (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Local 193 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Local 208 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Local 222 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Local 227 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Local 235 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Local 245 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Local 257 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Local 254 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Local 243 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Local 266 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Local 294 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Local 298 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Local 299 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Local 311 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Local 327 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Local 333 (out of existence, March, 1951) (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Local 417 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Local 425 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  newspaper clipping
- Local 438 (no record) (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Local 456 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Local 461 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Local 485 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Local 490 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Local 505 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Local 527 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Local 536 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Local 538 (no record of merged? - out of existence?) (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Local 543 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  1 photograph; negative
- Local 573 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Local 585 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Local 593 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Local 593 Chicago CIE -- Nov '59 - Corniskeep? Park Crew (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Local 595 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Local 632 (out Sept. 1964) (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Local 640 (merged with 76 and 150) Oswego, NY (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Local 654 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Local 661 (out Jan. 1958) (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Local 713 (Out Aug. 1957) (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Local 969 (out March 1, 1960) (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Local 738 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Local 741 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- Local 743 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- Local 828 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Local 835 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- Local 847 - Memphis, TN (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Local 859 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Local 861 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Local 863 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- Local 867 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- Local 878 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- Local 879 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- Local 883 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- Local 886 (Box 23, Folder 74)
- Local 893 (Box 23, Folder 75)
- Misc. Union Photographs (Box 23, Folder 76)
- Las Vegas (Box 23, Folder 77)
- HERE pictures (Box 23, Folder 78)
- 48th Annual AFL State Convention (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Convention, California State Federation of Labor, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  The Armory - Santa Barbara, Aug. 25-29, 1952
- Annual Banquet, Calif. State Council of Culinary Workers, Bartenders and Hotel Service Employees, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Rodger Young Auditorium - Los Angeles, August 28, 1949
- Business Session State Convention, Calif. State Federation of Labor (A.F.L.), 1948 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Long Beach Municipal Auditorium, Sept. 27-Oct. 2, 1948
- 34th General Convention, Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  April 22 to 27, 1957, Conrad Hilton Hotel, Chicago, Ill.
- Culinary Art Exhibit, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  Sponsored by the Cooks and Pastry Cooks Union Local No. 88, 34th General Convention; Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union AFL-CIO; April 22 to 27, 1957; Conrad Hilton Hotel; Chicago, Ill.
- Business Session, Calif. State Council of Culinary Workers, Bartenders and Hotel Service Employees, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  Long Beach; Sept. 24-26, 1948
- Business Session, Calif. State Council of Culinary Workers, Bartenders and Hotel Service Employees, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Los Angeles; Aug. 27, 1949 - [2 copies]
- California State Council of Culinary Workers, Bartenders, and Hotel Service Employees, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Fairmont Hotel - San Francisco, California; December 6, 1958
- Testimonial Dinner to Thomas a. Lenehan, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  President - Cleveland Federation of Labor; Mayfair Casino - May 11, 1936
- Unlabeled Convention Photograph (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Dinner tendered to Delegates attending H.&R.E.I.A. and B.I.L. of America Convention, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  by United Hebrew Waiters Union, Branch of Local 7; Roosevelt Hall; August 14, 1933; Chicago; Photograph is ripped and brittle
- Dinner in Honor of General President Flore, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  Given by the Local Joint Executive Board of Philadelphia; February 24, 1942-Stephen Girard Hotel -- Photograph is ripped and brittle
- Two unlabeled pencil sketches (Box 24, Folder 14)
  one of a woman's face, and on the flip side is one of men at a meeting
- Negatives belonging to the sketch of the woman in folder 14 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Photographs and Negatives (Box 24, Folder 16)
  13 photographs; negatives; graphics
- Above the Law (Box 24, Folder 17)
  graphics for an advertisement
- Imperial Palace Photograph; Sun Dial Photograph (Box 24, Folder 18)
  matching negatives
- General Assembly of Caribe Hilton Hotel Employees (Box 24, Folder 19)
  collective bargaining photos - 3 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Portrait photographs of Union Leaders (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Original Photos (Stand ups) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Note on box they came in is dated July 25, 1996; No other notes on photographs; 16 photographs
- Unlabeled photographs (Box 25, Folder 4)
  2 photographs, mounted on display boards
- UFCW convention/meeting (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Roulette wheel (Box 25, Folder 6)
  and negative
- Group Photograph (Box 25, Folder 7)
  Union leaders?
- Contact sheets (Box 25, Folder 8)
- 41st General Convention; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 41st General Convention; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Two Chefs (Box 25, Folder 11)
  Photograph, with no labeling
- UFCW Convention (Box 25, Folder 12)
- UFCW Convention (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Nov. 15, 1979 - Photograph (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Harry Truman Photograph (Box 25, Folder 15)
- American Federation o f Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  Nov. 19, 1979
- GEB - 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Carol Davison Photographs (Box 25, Folder 18)
  Research for Undergraduate Degree; Seattle, WA -- 10 photographs
- Sign (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America Affiliated with American Federation of Labor, Recognizes this house as a Union House and worth the support of Organized Labor.; pulled from box 25 and rehoused here
- Slides (Box 26, Folder 2)
  15 slides
- Slides (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Negatives (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Slides (Box 26, Folder 5)
  18 slides
- Negatives (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Imperial Palace; Playground (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Advertising Photographs (Box 26, Folder 8)
  15 photographs; graphics
- Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Las Vegas 1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Negatives (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Slides (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Aug-Oct 1994 - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 1)
- July-Aug 1994 - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Oct-Nov 1994 - Contact Sheets, Negatives and Slide (Box 27, Folder 3)
  1 Slide
- Dec 1994-Jan 1995 - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Jan-May 1995 - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Oct-Dec 1996 - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Slides and Contact Sheets (Box 27, Folder 7)
  211 slides
- Nov-Dec 1996 Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Commonsense Economics (CD-ROM photos) (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Contact Sheets (Box 27, Folder 11)
- July-Aug 1995 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Sept-Nov 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Nov-Dec 1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- July-Aug 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Aug-Sept 1996 -- Contact Sheets, Photograph Negatives, Slides (Box 28, Folder 5)
  40 slides
- Jan-June 1999 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Jan-Feb 1996 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 8)
- March-May 1996 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 9)
- May-June 1996 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 10)
- July 1997 -- Contact Sheets, Negatives and Slides (Box 28, Folder 11)
  108 slides
- Aug-Nov 1997 -- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Kmart (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Daycare - Chinatown Daycare Center (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Historical - Chinese (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Daycare - Chinatown Daycare Center - Black and White (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Daycare - Chinatown Daycare Center - (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Shops (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Shops (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Darrel Ward (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Warnaco (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Pamphlets (Box 29, Folder 11)
- NAACP and Philly GEB 10/9/2002 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Fall 2002 Rally (Box 29, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board (Barney's) (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Retirees (Box 29, Folder 15)
- International (Box 29, Folder 16)
- International-South Africa (Box 29, Folder 17)
- International - Philippines (Box 29, Folder 18)
  1 photograph; 2 slides
- International-Mauritiania (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Anastasias - Mexico (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Providence Journal (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Bruce Raynor (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Cintas Press Conference and Action at NLRB, California (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 25)
  13 photographs; 2 slides
- Jack Sheinkman (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Clara Lemlich - IL6 - Historical (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Maida Springer Kemp (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Historical - Tenement Museum (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Historical - Sebastian Liberty (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Triangle Fire 1911 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Triangle Fire (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Grouped Photographs (Box 29, Folder 33)
  147 photographs
- Grouped photographs (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Marshalls (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Elco Home Fashions, Hamilton Ontario; Photos by David Smiley (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Mission Workers (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Centro De Corte (Box 29, Folder 38)
- The Graduate Rally (Box 29, Folder 39)
- H and M Advertising (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Panoramic photographs - located in box 2OP (Box 32, Folder 1)
  515--104--b--2--a ----- 14 photographs -- group shots taken at conventions
- I'd rather go nekkid - June 2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  100 slides
- Warnaco (Box 30, Folder 2)
  CD/DVD pulled from this folder and labeled as Box 43 and placed in CD/DVD cabinet
- San Francisco Protest - 2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  CD/DVD pulled and placed in CD/DVD cabinet labeled Box 44
- Immigration (Box 30, Folder 4)
  102 slides; 23 photographs
- Immigration rights rally - 9 Oct-2002 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Brylane (Box 30, Folder 6)
  3 CD/DVDs removed and place in CD/DVD cabinet labeled as box 45, 46, 47; .105 photographs
- Fred's -- Memphis -- 2002 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  24 slides; 37 photographs; 1 CD/DVD - Fred's fired workers for posters - 6/14 March - removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet, labeled box 48
- DSC (Box 30, Folder 8)
  7 photographs; 1 CD/DVD - UNITE! Portraits, 2/22/2003 - removed and placed in CD/DVD cabinet and labeled box 49
- GAP Rally @ UCLA - 8/2002 with Raynor (Fall 2002) (Box 30, Folder 9)
  55 slides; 30 photographs
- Stand against sweatshops: A call for justice at GUESS? (Box 31, Folder 1)
- HERE Communication Dept. - Enlarged Photographs (Box 31, Folder 2)
  27 photographs - this file folder was originally housed in the Mapcase
- Local Union 8 - Seattle Headquarters (Box 33)
  - Local Union 8 - Seattle Headquarters (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Local 26 Photographs (Box 34)
  - Local 26 Photographs (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Liz Claiborne-Contract Campaign (Box 35)
  - Liz Claiborne - Contract Campaign - 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    pulled from an unnumbered folder in box 29
- Levis Health and Safety Training 2002 (Box 36)
  - Levis Health and Safety Training 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- UNITE Convention Gift Photo - July 2003 (Box 37)
  - UNITE Convention Gift Photo - July 2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Photo Director by Picasa (Box 38)
  - Photo Director by Picasa (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Brylane Celebration (Box 39)
  - Brylane Celebration (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Levis San Antonio Photos - Dec 3-4, 2001 (Box 40)
  - Levis San Antonio Photos - Dec 3-4, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- UNITE: Jesse Jackson - 6/14/2003 - (Box 41)
  - UNITE - Jesse Jackson - NCRM - Memphis, TN - 6/14/2003 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Jim Taynan Wall Street - 30/7/2002 (Box 42)
  - Jim Tynan Wall Street 30/7/2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    LAYLA --- pulled from an unnumbered folder in box 29
- UNITE - 4/28/2003 - WARNACO (Box 43)
  - UNITE! 4/28/2003; WARNACO (Box 43, Folder 1)
    1 CD/DVD removed from box 30 f2
- UNITE Jerry Hall (Box 44)
  - UNITE Jerry Hall (Box 44, Folder 1)
    1 CD/DVD removed from box 30 f 3
- Brylane Indy -- 1/29/2003 for UNITE (Box 45)
  - Brylane Indy 1/29/2003 for UNITE (Box 45, Folder 1)
    1 CD/DVD removed from box 30 f6
- Clark Jones, UNITE Brylane - 11/26/2002 (Box 46)
  - Clark Jones, UNIITE Brylane - 11/26/2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- UNITE - Brylane (Box 47)
  - UNITE - Brylane (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Freds fired workers for posters - 6/14 march (Box 48)
  - Fred's Fired Workers for Posters - 6/14 March (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1 CD/DVD removed from box 30 f7
- UNITE! Portraits -- 2/22/2003 (Box 49)
  - UNITE! Portraits - 2/22/2003 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    1 CD/DVD removed from box 30 f8
- Display boards -- Photos mounted on foam display boards (Box 50, Folder 1)